# **Gergely SZOLLOSI** – DevOps Engineer

### About me

**DevOps** professional with ~8 years experience. Self-motivated team player who enjoys automation and serverless technology (scripting: Ruby, Python). Skilled in Cloud technology: mainly AWS (4+ years). Gained knowledge in continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) pipelines as well as configuration management tools (Puppet, Chef). Primarily supported Linux operation systems (Ubuntu, RedHat); experienced in Agile, Scrum environments. Has insight into management, administration and IT operation environments.

## Experience

#### Career break - EXPLORER

February 2019 - August 2019

- Travelling across South East Asia for 6 months.
- Expanding IT knowledge: passed Docker and Jenkins Certification, ongoing progress on AWS Developer Associate as well as learning new technologies (i.e.: Ansible, Terraform)

#### FanDuel - DevOps Engineer

June 2018 - December 2018 (Contractor - Edinburgh, United Kingdom – 1 extension)

Participating in and resolving various tasks on demand that could be grouped as:

- cost saving and infrastructure cleanup activities
- maintaining infrastructure of and access to RPDM and RPI systems (Redpoint)
- automation tasks and notification system
- resolving basic security problems, potential risks

#### **Accxia -** Customer Success Manager

October 2017 - May 2018 (Fully remote)

Dealing with external customers, changing internal workflows, configuring internal tools (Atlassian) to improve customer experience (i.e.: demo environment; different platform for infra). Introduced various sessions (learning, planning) and restructured internal workflows to boost effectiveness of the team. Onsite customer visits and helped out with consultancy work too.

#### FanDuel - DevOps Engineer

October 2016 - September 2017 (Edinburgh, United Kingdom)

Looking after FanDuel AWS Cloud infrastructure using nearly the entire range of AWS services. Managing infrastructure's software with Puppet. Responsible of migrating the whole Redis infrastructure and refactoring Puppet code.

#### **Cloudreach -** DevOps Engineer

February 2015 - September 2016 (Edinburgh, United Kingdom)

Working in Cloud operations (mainly AWS and Azure): resolving infra and operation system level issues for Managed Services Customers (email, phone). Automation (Ruby, Chef) is widely used to manage infrastructure, monitoring, deployment and patching. Delivering regular Service Reviews for customers, providing recommendations based on the analysis of the infrastructure's performance. Developing new IT customer portal (ServiceNow).

#### **Adaptavist -** Application Support Analyst

November 2012 - June 2014 (London, United Kingdom)

Providing support for technical and non-technical users in regards to Atlassian applications. Fixing plugin bugs, resolving any application faults and performing application upgrades.

#### Nokia Siemens Networks - SOFTWARE ENGINEER

February 2011 - September 2012 (Budapest, Hungary)

Delivering solutions in regards to the Mobile Switching Centre's software (codec negotiations, signalling, routing, ...) as a 3rd level support engineer. Analysing logs, reproducing and fixing problems, writing change notes.

+44 7751 120 485

g.szollosi.job@gmail.com



#### Certifications

Edinburgh, Scotland

AWS SysOps Administrator - Associate (Expired March 2018) AWS Solution Architect - Associate (Expired June 2017) Docker Certified Associate (Sept. 2019 - Sept. 2021) Certified Jenkins Engineer (CJE) 2019 Architecting Microsoft Azure Solutions (70-534) PRINCE2® Foundation Examination ServiceNow Certified System Administrator ITIL® Foundation Certificate in ITSM Project Administration in JIRA (Until December 2019) Scrum Master (Expired March 2019)

### Skills/Technologies

Strong organization skill

Open-mindedness

Volunteering (OTAs booking, Photography)

Docker, AWS, Jenkins, Linuxacademy.com

Entire AWS services (EC2, RDS, Lambda, ElastiCache, IAM, S3. etc.)

Cloudhealth

RPDM/RPI, Powershell

Jenkins, CI/CD

Sparkleformation (Infrastructure as a Code)

**REST API** 

Management

Changing workflows

JIRA, ServiceDesk, Confluence, Bamboo, etc.

Tempo team management and planning

Redhat

IaC: CloudFormation / Sparkleformation

AWS, Azure, Google Apps for Enterprise

ElastiCache / Redis

Python scripting, Puppet, Ubuntu administration, Jenkins, GitHub build pipelines, r10k, automation

Graylog, Datadog

Splunk, Ruby, Chef, Linux, Windows MSSQL, Apache, Tomcat, Zenoss, Git Salesforce, ServiceNow, SLA, ITSM Incident and Change Management (RFC and P1 report), part of CAB, change and code review (git)

Confluence, JIRA, Bamboo Java EE, Git, Ruby Ubuntu, Support

MSC, codec negotiation, signaling

Analyzing logs, reproducing issues: Writing module and functional test

Understanding RFC, 3GPP

Education